

ABDUT ME

I am an IT Specialist with over 4 years of experience in information security and network configuration. Knowledgeable with variety of operating system, networking, and troubleshooting.

I am a flexible and experienced administrator with excellent time management skills. I am a good communicator with proven inter-personal skills and I am used to working in a team whose also being capable of using own initiative. Am skilled in dealing with problems in a resourceful manner and negotiating to achieve beneficial agreement. I am always enthusiastic to leam and undertake new challenges.

Skills

Masks

Microsoft Office Word

Microsoft Office Excel

Microsoft Office PowerPoint

Windows Operating System
Linux Operating System
Data Security & Administration
PfSense Firewall & Configuration
Network Connectivity & Configuration
Windows Server 2012R Configuration
Structured Cabling, LAN & WAN
Configuration
IT Infrastructure & Implementation

IPv4 Addressing: Network ID's & Subnet

LEANDRO-ANDRIE VENTURA



#3 Junji St. Rolling Hills Subd. Brgy. Kaligayahan, Novaliches, Quezon City



+63977-211-8535

andrie0604@gmail.com

Experiences

ABL Technical Services (August 2020 – Present) (Full-time)
IT Support Engineer, Network Administrator & System Administrator
(Dubai, UAE)

- Full-time Network Engineer & Hardware Engineer
- Structured Cabling, LAN & WAN Network Solution
- Web & SEO Developer
- WordPress Developer
- WD MyCloud File Server Administrator
- SQL Database & Administrator
- Installation, configuring, maintaining & testing operation system
- Troubleshooting, diagnosing & resolving hardware, software and other network & and system problems
- Coordinating computer network access and uses

GTXGaming.co.uk (June 2020 – Present) (Part-time) WordPress Developer (Dubai, UAE)

- Designing UX & UI
- Front & Back-end Developer
- HTML, CSS & JavaScript Specialist
- PHP & MySQL
- Website maintenance & updates

KabSlash IT Inc. (2018 - 2020) Network Engineer (Makati, Philippines)

- Database & Administrator Configuration
- Structured Cabling, LAN & WAN Network Solution
- Firewall & Network Configuration
- Hardware & Software Troubleshooting & Maintenance
- Hardware & Software Implementation & Configuration
- VoIP Installation, IPPABX, Telephony
- CCTV Installation & Access Control
- Installing, configuring, maintaining and testing operation system
- Access Point Implementation
- Protecting data, software, and hardware by coordinating, planning, and Implementing network security measures
- Troubleshooting, diagnosing and resolving hardware, software and other Network and system problems

Education

STI College - Fairview (2011 - 2015)

Graduate – Diploma in Information Technology Major in Programming